

Vanya Yepez

JR Front End Developer

vanya.yepez@gmail.com 55 9170 9103

About

Highly motivated with extensive experience in technical support, customer service and front-end web development.

Leveraging two years of experience as a Web Content Support Analyst, where I honed my skills to effectively diagnose and resolve complex front-end issues while ensuring exceptional client satisfaction. Driven by a passion for problem-solving and learning

Education

CCPM, 2002 - 2005

Tech Certification in Graphic Design and Programming

High School, 2004

High School Diploma, Architecture

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JQuery
- Javascript
- Customer Service
- Tech Support

Contact

vanya.yepez@gmail.com 55 9170 9103 Mexico City, Mexico

Experience

Web Content Analyst - Q4 Inc. Sep 2022 - Present - Mexico City

Updates to the IR websites of our publicly traded clients. Facilitation of high impact front-end content updates.

Customer Service Specialist - TTEC Nov 2021 - Jun 2022 - Mexico City

Tech Support for Verizon iOS and Android

Problem Solving

Freelancer - Cotton Candy Studios 2017 - 2021 - Mexico City

Computer Repair and Technical Support

Web Design - Front-End and UI/UX Game Design - Unity, C#

Client Acquisition

